http://carlist.com/privacy.php

carlist.com
Back to carlist.com
CLICK HERE TO CHANGE YOUR PRIVACY CONSENT SETTINGS
EZOIC SERVICE PRIVACY POLICY
carlist.com ("Website") uses a third party technology called Ezoic.
INFORMATION ABOUT OUR ORGANIZATION AND WEBSITE
Ezoic is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect lawfully in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679).
Ezoic's principal activities are:
Website analytics
Website personalization
Website hosting
Our privacy policy covers Ezoic Inc., Ezoic Limited and this Website:
Ezoic Inc.
6023 Innovation Way, Carlsbad, California, United States
Ezoic Limited
Northern Design Centre, Abbott's Hill, Gateshead, NE8 3DF United Kingdom
DATA
In order to provide our products and services and related support, it is necessary for Ezoic to transfer your personal data outside of the European Union.  In such case, the data controller for this data for EU residents is Ezoic Inc. having it’s registered offices at 6023 Innovation Way, Carlsbad, California, United States.  All questions of requests regarding the processing of data may be addresses to data@ezoic.com
PROVIDING VISITORS WITH ANONYMOUS ACCESS
If you do not consent to such collection, you can access this website without disclosing your personal data.
AUTOMATIC COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
Ezoic records data about the individuals and the traffic to this website. Ezoic is this website's limited agent (and data controller in the EU context) for the purpose of providing Internet data and optimization services. Ezoic may use this data to improve its service or enable other services (e.g., using visitor traffic logs or data posted through the service to improve the optimization of other websites).
Personal Information
Ezoic may collect personal information as defined in GDPR (such as IP address and a unique id in a cookie) about visitors to your website for the purposes of statistics, analytics and personalization. In addition, Ezoic works with numerous third parties for the collection and storage of data and the providing of analytics and advertising services.
Use of Personal Information
Purpose/Activity
Type(s) of Data
Lawful basis for processing
To improve user experience
Identity
Technical
Usage
Your information helps us to provide you with a more pleasant, efficient experience on this website that may be customized to how you or others respond to content and ads on this or other websites.
To improve ad performance
Identity
Technical
Usage
Your information helps us to optimize the placement, size, timing and number of ads displayed to you. It enables us to make smart decision that help this website owner earn money but reduce the disruption of ads on your experience.
To improve content creation
Identity
Technical
Usage
Your information helps us learn what content you care about and enjoy and, the style of content you like and what you engage the most with. This helps us produce more content and features that you might like.
To improve website performance
Identity
Technical
Usage
Your information helps us measure various performance metrics about our site, such as site speed, so that we can improve the performance of this site.
PROCESSING OF DATA AND CONSENT
We will process the data we collect about you to improve the operation of this and other websites. This information helps us make decisions about what content to show, how it should be formatted, the number, size and placement of advertisements and how content should be delivered to individuals. THis information is also used for analysis of performance and reporting.
USE OF APPLICATION LOGS
Our servers automatically record information (“Application Log Data”) created by your use of this website. Application Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, search terms, and cookie information. We use this information to diagnose and improve our services. Except as stated in section (Data Retention), we will either delete the Application Log Data or remove any account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or email address, after 48 months.
DATA RETENTION
The personal information we collect is retained for no longer than necessary to fulfil the stated purposes in section “PROCESSING OF DATA AND CONSENT” above or for a period specifically required by law or regulation that Ezoic is obligated to follow. Personal data used to fulfil verification of certain types of services such as SSL certificate, payments, and billing will be retained for a minimum of 5 years depending on the class of product or service and may be retained in either a physical or electronic format. Even if you request deletion or erasure of your data, we may retain your personal data to the extent necessary and for so long as necessary for our legitimate business interests or performance of contractual obligations. After the retention period is over, Ezoic securely disposes or anonymizes your personal information in order to prevent loss, theft, misuse, or unauthorized access.
CONFIDENTIALITY / SECURITY
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: unauthorized access improper use or disclosure unauthorized modification unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation
DATA ACCESS & DELETION
You have the right to view information that we have collected about you and to request deletion of any personal information we may have. You can use this data lookup tool to complete these actions.
Below is a list of cookies that are commonly set on this website.
Below is a list of usage, technical and identify metrics that are commonly stored and processed when you use this website
Your location information, including country, state, city, metro and postal code
The webpage your were at before this website
The type of browser you use and the version
The brand and operating system of your device
What time zone you're in and what time it is there
What pages on this site you visit
How you interact with this website, including time spent, how much you scroll and your mouse movements
The size of your devices screen and the size of the browser on that screen
What content you share on the page
If you copy and paste content on this website
What ad or link you clicked on to arrive at this website
The type of internet connection you use and your ISP or service provider
How long it takes for this website's content to get transfered to your browser, load in your browser and render
The weather where you are currently located
Your age and gender
Your ip address
A unique id so that we can recognize you
What ads you click on
Cookies
Cookie NameCategoryDescriptionDurationezovuuid_#NecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify a visit by you to this website. Used for analytics and personalization of your experience.30 minezovuuidtime_#NecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record the time of your visit to this website so different visits can be differentiated from each other.2880 minwordpress_test_cookieNecessaryWordPress sets this cookie when you navigate to the login page. The cookie is used to check whether your web browser is set to allow, or reject cookies.active_template::#NecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store which template you are viewing on this website.ez_pub_siteNecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to only show the site with Ezoic's features enabled. ezCMPCookieConsentNecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track when a user consents to cookies.ez_rdr_countNecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track redirectsez_rdrNecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track redirects.wordpress_logged_in_#NecessaryUsed by Wordpress sites to identify the user.wp-settings-time-#NecessaryStores the id of the wordpress user that is logged in.wp-settings-#NecessaryStores the settings of the wordpress user that is logged in.__utmt_eNecessaryUsed to throttle the speed of requests to the server.__utmt_fNecessaryUsed to throttle the speed of requests to the server.wp-postpass_#NecessaryUsed by Wordpress sites for security / login purposeswordpress_sec_#NecessaryUsed by Wordpress sites for security purposes.ez_view_original_onlyPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to show the original site without Ezoic's features.ez_view_optimized_onlyPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to show the optimized site with Ezoic's features.ez_view_optimized_only
PreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to show the original site without Ezoic's features.speed_no_processPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to turn off site speed features for this user.sitespeed_previewPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to allow this user to preview certain site speed features.ez_ad_position_versionPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to determine if they use the Ad Tester product for this user, used by the Ad Tester extension.ezpicker_showallPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to tell the ezpicker app to show all placeholders.ezpicker_nocachePreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to tell the ezpicker app to run without using the cache.ezpickerPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to turn on ezpicker_gat_gtag_UA_#StatisticsUsed by Google Analytics for user tracking._gidStatisticsUsed to distinguish users by Google Analyticsezoadgid_#StatisticsRecords an id that to your age and gender category.
For example, id 923 might be for males between 20 and 30 years old.30 minezoab_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to split test different features and functionality.120 minezoref_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the referring domain (the website you were at before you can to this website).120 min__qcaStatisticsCollects anonymous data on the user's visits to the website, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded with the purpose of generating reports for optimising the website content.ezopvc_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the number of pages that you have viewed on this site in this session.30 min_gaStatisticsUsed to distinguish users by Google Analyticsezux_tos_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record the amount of time you have spent on this website.ezux_et_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record the amount of time that you engaged with content on this website. Used for analytics purposes to improve user experience.ezCMPCCSStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track when a user consents to statistics cookies.ezux_lpl_#Statistics Used by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record the time that you loaded the last page on this website.ezutm_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the list of utm parameters that they have access to.ezosuigeneriscStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify you across different websites on the internet so your experience can be customized.ezoawesome_#Statistics Used by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, for fraud and invalid activity detection.ezuz_ifep_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record whether you have engaged with the content on this site.
Used for analytics purposes to improve user experience.ezovid_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify a visit by you to this website. Used for analytics and personalization of your experience.ezouid_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify you as a visitor on this website. Used for analytics and personalization of your experience.ezosuigenerisStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify you across different websites on the internet so your experience can be customized.ezostid_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to test different features and functionality and to record which features and functionality are available to you so you receive a consistent experience.ezdsStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the pixel size of your screen to help personalize your experience and ensure content fits.ez_recommended_pagesStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track users visiting from the recommended pages widget.AMP_ECID_EZOICStatisticsUsed by personalization and analytics company Ezoic for statistics on Accelerated Mobile PagesezouspvvStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track how many pages a user has visited.ezouspvhStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track how many pages a user has visited since their last visit.ezouspvaStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track how many pages a user has visited all time.ezepvvStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track which pages this user has viewed.ezohwStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the pixel size of your browser to help personalize your experience and ensure content fits.__utmzStatisticsCollects data on where the user came from, what search engine was used, what link was clicked and what search term was used. Used by Google Analytics.__utmbStatisticsRegisters a timestamp with the exact time of when the user accessed the website. Used by Google Analytics to calculate the duration of a website visit.__utmaStatisticsCollects data on the number of times a user has visited the website as well as dates for the first and most recent visit. Used by Google Analytics.__utmcStatisticsRegisters a timestamp with the exact time of when the user leaves the website. Used by Google Analytics to calculate the duration of a website visit.__gadsMarketingUsed to register what ads have been displayed to the user.ezdgMarketingUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store demographic information like age and gender.
A list of Vendors that may be used on this website
Data Usage Purposes
Necessary
Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
Preferences
Preference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in.
Statistics
Statistic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.
Marketing
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.
Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or you wish to unsubscribe from our site and services you may contact us using the information below or by writing to us at:
11265 Wisteria Way
Auburn, USA 95603
United States
Summary of Requests If you'd like to see a summary of the requests to know user information, requests to delete user information and requests to opt-out of ccpa compliance that this business has received:
https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/carlist.com/annualRequestSummary
regarding carlist.com
Email:louannhammond@yahoo.com
